Judy Lee

Pharmacist, Pharmacist in Charge

Newtown, PA - Email me on Indeed: indeed.com/r/Judy-Lee/00dbc8e35ec48a32

Pharmacist with a PharmD degree licensed in New Jersey, New York, Pennsylvania, and Tennessee. Ten years of retail experience as a pharmacist and three years of hospital experience as a pharmacy intern. Patient service oriented and dedicated to providing the highest standard of care. Excels at teamwork, conflict resolution, and making sound decisions under pressure. Completed MTM certificate program. Authorized to work in the US for any employer

WORK EXPERIENCE

Pharmacist, Pharmacist in Charge

CVS Pharmacy - Yardley, PA - August 2004 to February 2015

Process prescriptions including interpreting, entering, and filling prescriptions

- ♦ Verify prescription Perform quality assurance check for drug-drug interactions, drug-disease interaction, and perform drug-utilization review
- ♦ Responsible for pharmacy workflow and budget, scheduling and hiring technicians, and maintaining pharmacy inventory including ordering narcotics
- ♦ Handling pharmacy-related problems including incident resolution and documentation, prescription returns and refunds, drug recalls, third party issues
- ♦ Answer drug-related information questions including recommending OTC medication for self-treatment
- ♦ Support and counsel customers on their medications and medical devices
- ♦ Perform monthly drug expiration check, CII inventory, and overstock returns
- ♦ Interpret, prepare, and label compounds
- ♦ Proactively build customer relationships, meet customer needs, and responsible for resolving customer problems promptly
- ♦ Make and take in doctor phone calls for new prescriptions, refill authorization and for prescription verification
- Administer vaccination
- Counseling patient on medication adherence and cost saving opportunities

Pharmacy Intern

CVS Pharmacy - New York, NY - April 2000 to August 2004

Type prescriptions into the computer, count, and restock medications

- ♦ Make and take doctor phone calls for refill authorization and for prescription verification
- ♦ Bill and call insurance company on prescription rejects, vacation overrides, and eligibility verification
- ♦ Make and take in prescription transfers
- ♦ Support and counsel customers on their medications
- ♦ Perform weekly inventory return to stock
- ♦ Order medications from Cardinal and Mark Stevens
- ◆ Perform weekly item verification procedure Cycle Count

Professional Rho Chi Pharmacy Honor Society - Member Membership: Phi Eta Sigma National Honor Society - Member Golden Key National Honor Society - Member

Pharmacy Intern

Cornell-Weill New York Presbyterian - New York, NY - September 2002 to May 2004

Prepare and fill medication orders

- ♦ Prepare intravenous medications using aseptic techniques
- ♦ Make and answer doctor and nurses' phone calls for missing medications, stat medications, and medication approval
- ♦ Provide answers to drug information questions
- ♦ Deliver narcotics and other medications to floors
- ♦ Fill and perform cart exchange

EDUCATION

Doctor of Pharmacy

St. John's University - Jamaica, NY May 2004

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

Skills: Rx 2000, Internet explorer, Micromedex, Medline, IPA, Facts and Comparison, MS PowerPoint, Drug information skills